IL Cafe we have you
covered welcome to Il Cafe my name is
shal and today we're going to be
catching up with a member of the ICC
Lombard family and that person is
abishek saraf and he's here to tell us
about two offerings and I'm quite
certain you'll walk away with more
information than you have right now as
we begin this conversation one of them
is called uh the Health Advantage policy
and the other one is be fit Rider so
both these are what we're going to be
catching up with abishek about well
thank you so much abishek and welcome to
Il Cafe thank you J so certainly I will
explain you the both the benefit Health
Advantage and benefit we'll start with
Health Advantage first so Health
Advantage is a Comprehensive Health
insurance policy which cover all your
Healthcare needs so it has a cover from
impatient to occupation and also have an
ID like the C personal exgen and some of
the key benefit which include in this
product is a worldwide cover where we
cover both plann and unpl treatment then
we have air ambulance cover which is
covered up to some insured Home Care
treatment where a doctor has prescribed
that the treatment can be taken at home
so this feature is very useful and it
was very useful at time of CO as well
then we have unlimited Tel consultation
where we cover 247 Tel consultation a
customer can connect with the doctor 24
into 7 from I take care app we have a
research benefit which cover also same
illness so as you know C uh people buy a
some in short suppose I'm on average of
10 L some in short and what happen if
that some insured exhaust during the
policy period so we have that unique
benefit research benefit for the same
inless a customer can basically top up
the Su insure from 10 plus 10 so that's
a great benefit a customer can have and
in addition to that we also have
guaranteed cumulative bonus so why it's
called granted is basically uh every
claim fee year we give 20% of the summ
ins short as a bonus and in case a
customer claims so we don't de with
anything so that's the reason we call it
granted So 20% every year maximum up to
100% okay now every customer have
different needs so everybody can opt for
different add-ons by paying extra
premium example M benefit which is
covered at a Ving per of 9 months so
this again is a unique thing where uh in
the market people cover do such kind of
benefit of waiting period of couple of
three years but here we cover it after 9
months another thing where most of the
customer doesn't want to pay anything
out from the pocket in the hospital when
they go hospital at the time of
discharge there are a lot of La payables
where we the hospital the payment so now
with a add don't like claim protector a
customer can op this cover and basically
non- payable will also be covered in
this policy right another unique benefit
here to beat inflation we have a some
insur Proctor a unique cover where a
guaranteed percentage of some insur is
increased every year for example suppose
the inflation rate is 7% every year your
7% subm will increase respective of the
claim so there's nothing to do with the
claim it's just to beat inflation right
so these are the host of coverage which
we have in uh Health Advantage policy
which gives a flexibility to the
customer to make their own plan and take
the cover which they need right yeah
customer clearly at the focus or the
center of all that you have uh thought
of with respect to this particular
offering I can hear that abishek and I
really like the last point you about
beating inflation because that's really
on everybody's Minds uh whether it is
something like this a topic we're
discussing or you know buying a home or
anywhere at all but let me come to this
other reality that all of us are in
everything these days is online right so
why should someone consider buying this
um you know policy the Health Advantage
policy online what happens everybody
want to basically surf online and to
check each and every benefit by their
own so what happens so when you go buy
health insurance policy online you have
access to all the information and also
allow you to compare the policies with
other insurer and a customer can take
informed decision that's the reason
people go for buying online policies so
that they have the more information and
they can take informed decisions well
thank you for that PO it helps us
understand what the options are with
respect to you know getting hold of this
particular policy there's another one
you mentioned be fit Rider right at the
start of our conversation today so I
think it's time uh to get our viewers
some insights on what this is all about
what is beit Rider sure so so when we
launch V rer it was one of the unique I
think proposition in the market where we
were providing this OPD coverage which
was 100% cashless digital solution so
you don't have to visit anywhere or you
don't have to basically go anywhere to
Avail such kind of benefit this can be
done through your home through the I
take care app so it allows policy holder
to have all the discussion with your
general physician specialist super
Specialist or I doctor also online and
this facility is available 24 into 7
okay so this prod was kept in mind uh
that all your everyday Healthcare needs
apart from in patient hospitalization is
covered under this product so as we
already said it was a be is a beit rider
so on top of a base policy which you
have already taken you can buy this
cover okay and uh to add I just want to
add a couple of things more what are the
benefit which we have in bit cover so to
start with as I already said we have
aeration service where we cover physical
doctor consultation also and we also
cover uh 24 into 7 tele consultation
other than that we cover your Pharmacy
cost diagnostic cost Physiotherapy stion
and also today I think in today world
most of the people are op such kind of
feature like Di and nutrition consing so
everybody is conscious of the diet of
health and that facility Avail to our I
take
care absolutely and after the festive
season is over all the more reason to
actually focus on your diet that
particular angle is going to go for a
toss in sometime as all the sweets
really come out get rolled out uh you
know during navratri and certainly after
that in Diwali so useful pointer over
there but uh abishek tell me you know
how can someone aail of this caselist
claim service for the B fit Rider and
also another question that I had in my
mind uh you mentioned base health
insurance policy to which this can be uh
you know added on so which are the ones
from icsu Lombard that are eligible for
the betet rider so I will come back to
your second question first so if you
talk about the base policy like Health
Advantage all our Healthcare inmy policy
we'll have a beer option to the
customers now coming to the first
question uh how we can Avail it so as I
said it's a 100% digital solution so to
Avail this Services you need to download
I'll take care app register and then
select the respective service icon on
the app homepage to is the benefit for
example so if you Lo if you already have
a policy and if you log in with your
registered mobile number your policy
will be linked directly to app and on
the homepage you have a option like
telec consulation H so you can opt any
of the facility and you can Avail the
service so it's very uh I will say a
customer friendly uh app where you don't
require any kind of a basically
assistance so moving on right I want to
ask you a little bit more since you
mentioned dieticians um and we spoke
about that briefly a while ago as one of
the many categories little bit more I
think I think detail will be very
helpful for our viewers in terms of the
kind of healthcare professionals that
they can have access uh to Via this
health insurance
coverage yeah absolutely C so we have a
wide range of doctors and medical
professional who are basically we have
done atire start from the general
practitioner specialist super specialist
and I doctors so when we talk about
specialist we have seen the majority of
the take up in the consultation is from
specialist so like uh people are more in
like back p P shoulder pain so people
most of the people have availed such
kind of benefit apart from that we have
seen people have availed benefit like
for diabetes and hypertension which are
basically now a lifestyle kind of
disease where the most of the queries
has come across so what happen when we
have such kind of wide uh range of
doctors this ensure that they can
receive the care which every everyday
their healthare needs provide so now
what happens most of the people doesn't
know where to go to a such kind of
benefit like today I'm working in Mumbai
maybe I'm not my hometown so what happen
I don't know what kind of specialist I
need or where where to go so such kind
of a product like vit Rider where we
provide 100% solution online uh the
customer can opt The Specialist as for
their choice so this give an opt option
to the customer so that they can Avail
the benefit as per their choice without
going
anywhere understood and that point that
you made is so true right a lot of us
actually work outside of our hometowns
now uh have moved to cities Etc and
access to healthcare professionals
sometimes that itself is a first
question mark right who I seek out and
important to have raised that point I
imagine access to different Specialists
also as you underlined now if you were
to just summarize some of the key
benefits of both uh the offerings that
we spoke about the you know Health
Advantage policy and also beit Rider uh
what would you say to our listeners so
absolutely uh sh what i' like to say
definitely when you're looking for a
comprehensive health insurance coverage
which cover OPD as well as ipd this both
product solution provided by is Lombard
covers all the uh need of the customer
and top of that a customer in case of
they require a PA and CI cover also like
personal ex CI they can opt as an add-on
in Health Advantage so no doubt uh if a
customer is in India and looking for a
reliable HealthCare coverage uh customer
can opt for Health Advantage and people
it together well I think that completes
our understanding of two offerings from
the IC Lombard Universe in I Cafe today
and I'm super glad that they're able to
Spotlight you know different offerings
that we have that have the customer at
focus and address some of the common p
points that people have in their
experience to seek out good products in
this particular uh sector thank you so
much for talking to us abish and here's
wishing you and your family a very happy
festive season uh going forward in the
best of health of course thank you sh
same to you it's been a pleasure being
here and Shing information to all our
viewers